if we have to come back and we give you the
si hay que volver y os damos la
political promotion or I go there for a week
promoción política o me voy una semana
to see the critters with Fran or
ahí a ver los bichos con Fran o alguna
something, well, that's what you could do
cosa ya pues eso eso te lo podías hacer
yesterday I had lunch with my representative and
ayer comí con mi representante y
talking to him he said go there for a week
hablando con él me decía vete una semana
with Fran to record videos and take a
con Fran allí a grabar vídeos y haces
vacation I say wow man the truth is it
vacaciones digo bua tío la verdad que
could be fun but I don't know is there a
puede ser divertido pero no sé hay vuelo
direct flight from Madrid I can go alone there is a
directo desde Madrid yo puedo ir solo
direct flight from Madrid come on let's go Hold my
hay vuelo directo ya desde Madrid venga
drink damn Hold my drink let's date
vamos Aguántame el cubata [__] Aguántame
You set the date AB
el cubata pemos fech Tú pon la fecha AB
tell me April April it doesn't matter to me it's like
dime abril abril a m me da es si es que
I live here alone I live with Paloma and with
yo vivo aquí solo vivo con Paloma y con
300 critters okay listen to me I'm coming with
300 bichos vale escúchame me vengo con
my representative and a camera and we'll
mi representante y una cámara y la
have a rough time
liamos pard